MOSTAFA KHAIRALLA

SUMMARY

Talented Full Stack .NET Developer Interested in Power Platform | OutSystems with 2 years of experience leading projects through all phases of software development life cycle while maintaining strict deadlines. Improve functionality and performance by troubleshooting and analyzing systems to identify bugs and develop solutions. Skilled in implementing technologies including C#, ASPX, .NET Framework, SQL Server, and VS Code

EDUCATION

Faculty of Specific Education Department of Technology University

Overall Grade: Very Good Graduation Project Grade: Excellent Graduation year: 2020

2016 to 2020

Dubai

EMPLOYMENT

EGMaster

Full Stack Dot Net Developer

Alexandria June 2022 to Current

Oct. 2020 to Nov. 2021

Mar. 2020 to Oct. 2020

June 2020 to Sept. 2020

 $\mbox{l'm}$ currently working on Building an ERP system as well as and side outsystems projects

Business Eco System Cairo
Dot Net Developer Oct. 2021

Designed conceptual data model based on the requirement.

Developed charts for dashboards that shows the performance of point of sale program

Handled performance tuning.

Manipulated database for testing using SQL . Created Roles By using Asp.net Core

Created master data management

Created Role's and authentication from scratch

Created reports by using RDLC

Impress Digital Solution

Full Stack Dot Net Developer

Sharjah Investors Center
•Migrated Sharjah Investors Center From Web Form To asp Dot net Core

- designing reports and invoices by using Report Viewer
- Designed and implemented user interfaces By using C#
- · -Designing App main view using HTML, CSS, Java Script , JQuery

PROJECTS

Graduation Project (Attendance QR Code System)

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity framework, Mvc5, MS SQL server ,))

helps students to register attendance through Qr Code technology and through the program they can learn about attendance and absence

- Designing Web System
- Implementing new features and fixing problems
- •Designing SQL Database
- •Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap

Educational Platform: Technologies & Teols used (analysis and Designed application system to Help Students and

Technologies & Tools used (analysis and Designed application system to Help Students and Teachers, Html,Css,Java Script Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity

framework, Mvc5, MS SQL server)

- •Designing Web System
- •Implementing new features and fixing problems
- •Designing SQL Database
- •Designing App main view using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap

ProDinner

Web application for restaurant management

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity

framework, Mvc5, MS SQL server)

- Analyzed requirements and designed application and database schema.
- •Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap
- Coded, tested, debugged, and deployed applications

News Site

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity

framework, asp.net core , MS SQL server)

- Analyzed requirements and designed application and database schema.
- Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap
- Coded, tested, debugged, and deployed applications

Online Shopping Site

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entityframework, asp.net core , MS SQL server)

- Analyzed requirements and designed application and database schema.
- •Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap
- Coded, tested, debugged, and deployed applications



ACTIVITIES

 $Languages: C\#, Web: HTML5, CSS, Java Script\ , Angular 10, Jquery\ , ASP. NET\ (Core, MVC\ and\ Web\ Forms),$

Services: ASP.Net MVC API, REST APIWeb and Application Servers: IIS, Apache, Frameworks: .NET Framework, Entity Framework,

Design Patterns: Singleton, MVC, MVVM, Repository SDLC, Databases: Oracle, SQL Server, Agile Tools: Visual Studio, VS Code, Out systems, Power platform

Member at Egyptian Society for Science and Engineering (2018).